RG 071:003, Department of Housing Planning Maps
Connecticut State Library
- Dept. of Community Affairs. Planning Maps, circa 1943-1980
  - Vernon (Box 7)
    - Zoning map, 1963 March 8; Technical planning Associates; 15 x 13 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: VIII
    - Zoning map, 1963 March 8; Technical planning Associates; 15 x 13 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: IX
    - Zoning map, 1963 March 8; Technical planning Associates; 15 x 13 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: X
    - Zoning map, 1963 March 8; Technical planning Associates; 15 x 13 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: XI
    - Zoning map Bolton lake, 1963 March 8; Technical planning Associates; 29 x 16.25 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: XII
    - Bolton lake uses and occupancy, 1963 March 8; Technical planning Associates; 29 x 16.25 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 7)
    - Proposed zoning map, 1963 March 8; Technical planning Associates; 32 x 29 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
  - Waterbury (Box 7)
    - Renewal areas and projected dwelling displacement, undated; Planning and Renewal Associates; 35 x 35 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 7)
      701 project: Conn. P-6
    - Flood profiles in waterbury, undated; Planning and Renewal Associates; 24.5 x 49 in. (Box 7)
    - Schematic river cross-section, undated; Planning and Renewal Associates; 21.5 x 30 in. (Box 7)
    - Recommended flood zone, undated; Planning and Renewal Associates; 30.25 x 88 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 7)
    - Flood plain proposals, undated; Planning and Renewal Associates; 30.25 x 88 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 7)
    - Land development factors, undated; Planning and Renewal Associates; 35 x 36.25 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 7)
    - Street and thoroughfare plan, undated; Planning and Renewal Associates; 35 x 36.25 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 7)
    - Neighborhood plan, undated; Planning and Renewal Associates; 35 x 36.25 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 7)
    - Zoning map, 1971 November 1; 34.5 x 34 in. (Box 7)
  - Watertown (Box 8)
    - Base map - streets, 1964 May; Bryan & Panico Planning Consultants; 60 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 1500 feet (Box 8)
      plan number: II-A-1
    - watertown center, 1964 May; Bryan & Panico Planning Consultants; 30 x 19.25 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 8)
      plan number: II-A-3
    - Oakville center, 1964 September; Bryan & Panico Planning Consultants; 20 x 20 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 8)
      plan number: II-A-4
    - Generalized existing land use, 1964 May; Bryan & Panico Planning Consultants; 60 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 8)
      plan number: II-C-1
    - Dwelling unit distribution, 1964 May; Bryan & Panico Planning Consultants; 60 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 8)
    - Zoning map, 1955 April 1; 30 x 21 in.; 1 inch = 1700 feet (Box 8)
    - Zoning map, Watertown Fire District, 1943 November 2; 15 x 12 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 8)
  - Westbrook (Box 8)
    - Conditions affecting development, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 23.25 x 19.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 8)
    - Land use, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 23.25 x 19.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 8)
    - Existing water distribution, 1960 August; Technical Planning Associates; 23.25 x 19.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 8)
  - West Hartford (Box 8)
    - Zoning map, 1955 January 31; 22 x 16.5 in.; 1 inch = 1500 feet (Box 8)
    - Zoning map, 1957 September; 22 x 17 in.; 1 inch = 1500 feet (Box 8)
    - Zoning map, 1962 December; 22 x 17 in.; 1 inch = 1300 feet (Box 8)
    - Town of West Hartford, 1952 March 15; 25.5 x 33.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 8)
  - West Haven (Box 8)
    - Open space and recreation program, 1967-1980; 22 x 17 in. (Box 8)
    - Vacant properties 5 acres or more suitable for development, Goodkind & O'Dea, Planning Consultants; 40.5 x 29 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
  - Weston (Box 8)
    - Base map, undated; Frederick P. Clark and Associates; 76 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 600 feet (Box 8)
      701 project: Conn. P-73
    - Existing land use changes, undated; Frederick P. Clark and Associates; 76 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 600 feet (Box 8)
    - Existing land use changes, 1957-1967, undated; Frederick P. Clark and Associates; 76 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 600 feet (Box 8)
    - Proposed zoning map, 1969 March; Frederick P. Clark and Associates; 76 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 600 feet (Box 8)
    - Plan of development, 1969 January; Frederick P. Clark and Associates; 76 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 600 feet (Box 8)
    - Road improvement status, undated; Frederick P. Clark and Associates; 76 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 600 feet (Box 8)
    - Road maintenance responsibility, undated; Frederick P. Clark and Associates; 76 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 600 feet (Box 8)
    - Potential new dwelling units, 1967; Frederick P. Clark and Associates; 76 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 600 feet (Box 8)
    - Road functions, undated; Frederick P. Clark and Associates; 76 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 600 feet (Box 8)
    - Proposed plan, undated; Frederick P. Clark and Associates; 35.25 x 21.5 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 8)
    - Zoning map, 1965 July 1; Sanborn Map Company; 28.5 x 23 in.; 1 inch = 1500 feet (Box 8)
  - Wethersfield (Box 8)
    - Circulation plan, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 26 x 30.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 8)
      701 project: Conn. P-33
      plan number: IX-A-2, IX-B
    - Water distribution system, 1975; The Metropolitan District; 25 x 32.5 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 8)
    - Sanitary sewer system, 1975; The Metropolitan District; 25 x 32.5 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 8)
  - Willimantic (Box 8)
    - Zoning map, 1964 February; 15.5 x 22 in.; 1 inch = 900 feet (Box 8)
    - Fenton river water shed, 1972; 48 x 36 in. (Box 8)
  - Winchester (Box 8)
    - Zoning map, 1956 April 9; Technical Planning Associates; 17 x 18 in.; 1 inch = 2400 feet (Box 8)
      701 project: Conn. P-84
      plan number: 1 of 2
    - Zoning map, 1956 April 9; Technical Planning Associates; 17 x 18 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
      plan number: 2 of 2
  - Windsor Locks (Box 8)
    - Geologic map, 1960; Roger B. Colton; 30 x 18 in.; 1 inch = 24000 feet (Box 8)
  - Wolcott (Box 8)
    - New residental and street construction, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 46.5 x 34.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
    - Existing land use, 1962 October; Technical Planning Associates; 46.5 x 34.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
    - Plan of public facilities for schools, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 46.5 x 34.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 8)
    - New residental and street construction, 1944-1962, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 46.5 x 34.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
    - New residental and street construction, 1944-1962, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 46.5 x 34.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
    - Plan of public facilities for schools, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 46.5 x 34.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 8)
    - Existing land use, 1962 October; Technical Planning Associates; 46.5 x 34.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
  - Woodbridge (Box 8)
    - Major traffic patterns, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = .5 mile (Box 8)
    - Topography, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
    - Soil characteristics, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
    - Development characteristics, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
    - Building growth, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
    - Condition of roads, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
    - Utility services, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
    - Existing public facilities, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
    - Proposed land use, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
    - Population growth - distribution and sensities, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
    - Major street plan, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
    - Extension of public facilities, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
    - Zoning map, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 8)
      plan number: 15
    - Illustrative site plan, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 98 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 8)
    - Zoning map, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 98 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 8)
  - Woodstock (Box 8)
    - Plan of development, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 43 x 56 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 8)
      701 project: Conn. P-70
    - Slope map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 43 x 56 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 8)
    - Existing street classification, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 43 x 56 in. (Box 8)
    - Existing traffic volumes, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 43 x 56 in. (Box 8)
    - soils map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 43 x 56 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 8)
    - Population distribution map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 43 x 56 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 8)
    - Buildable land map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 43 x 56 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 8)
    - Detailed soils map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 43 x 56 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 8)
    - Land use map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 43 x 56 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 8)
    - Topographic map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 43 x 56 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 8)
    - Street improvement plan, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 43 x 56 in. (Box 8)